

# **LORALEE STARLA GENTRY**

FILM PRODUCTION & DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGN

832 - 444 - 9799

Ioraleestarla@me.com

5457 Laurel Canyon Blvd, #108 Valley Village, CA 91607

www.loraleestarla.com

### **ABOUT ME**

Recent graduate with extensive knowledge and experience in the Film, Visual Design, and Web Design fields.

Strong passion for creating and expanding stories portrayed through visual mediums.

Motivated to entertain and inspire communities through illustrative and interactive user experiences.

# **WORK HISTORY**



#### MEDIA PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

Eastern Washington University | Cheney, WA April 2014 - June 2015

Key member of a production team for EWU's extended campus, online division. Filmed events and interviews on location. Did production design, grip, lighting, and camera work for videos filmed in studio and on location. Compiled and organized HD, SD, audio, and still footage. Edited audio and video content along with



#### **BEAUTY ADVISOR**

Walgreens Drug Store | Seattle, WA August 2012 - June 2013

Greeted customers and assisted them with finding the right products for their specific needs. Organized and cleaned designated aisles of the store to create a better shopping experience for customers and move more merchandise. Rang up customers at the register and successfully handled cash, card, and check transactions.



#### SECRETARY ON THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS

Diverse Harmony | Seattle, WA October 2012 - June 2013

Board member for the 501(c)(3) non-profit Gay-Straight Alliance Youth Chorus of Seattle. Recorded official meeting minutes, kept a compilation of all important documents, and made decisions on behalf of the chorus by voting as a board member on financial, organizational, administrative, and creative issues.

# REFERENCES

- COREY BURGESS EASTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY
   Media Production Specialist | 509-359-6284 | coreyb@ewu.edu
- TIM SNYDER EASTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY
   Director of Eastern Online | 509-359-2033 | tlsnyder@ewu.edu
- MARY CUTHBERT WALGREENS
   Media Production Specialist | 206-709-4569

# **EDUCATION**

◆ EASTERN WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY
Cheney, WA | Sept 2013 - June 2015

Bachelor of Arts Degree Interdisiplinary Studies, focused in Film Production and Digital Media Design

◆ SEATTLE CENTRAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE Seattle, WA | April 2011 - June 2013

Associate of Arts Degree
General Studies

◆ CALIFORNIA POLYTECHNIC STATE UNIVERSITY San Luis Obispo, CA | Sept 2008 - June 2012 Studied Aerospace Engineering

◆ CLEAR LAKE HIGH SCHOOL Houston, TX | Sept 2004 - June 2008 Diploma

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

| • | PHOTOSHOP           |      | 90% |
|---|---------------------|------|-----|
| • | ILLUSTRATOR         | 65%  |     |
| • | PREMIERE PRO        |      | 90% |
| • | AFTER EFFECTS       | 75%  |     |
| • | HTML5               |      | 90% |
| • | CSS 3               |      | 90% |
| • | JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY   | 60%  |     |
| • | IWORKS/MICROSOFT OF | FICE | 95% |

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**







SOLVING









ININ

PEOPLE COMM SKILLS

COMMUNICATION PASSION